这使我不得不使用这门炮
吃吃这发
我能扛住你的炮弹
我也能
什么？
这是个难以对付的对手
英文字幕:
自动英文字幕
翻译，校对，润色，压制:
Bolshevik0
So as you guys can see the Type 90 has been announced for War Thunder patch 1.79
正如你们所见 90式即将在战雷的1.79版本中发布
we don't know, maybe I don't know, not from this dev blog of the 1.79 name
至少我还没看到开发者博客中有提及1.79版本的名字
such as you know assault advancing storm etc.
就是类似什么进化风暴之类的
I would love if the community could pick out the patch names
我希望新版本的名字能从社区中选择出来
with a filter ability
通过某种筛选机制
but I feel like that would just ruin the ability for a War Thunder to market their game
不过这也会毁掉战雷的游戏推广能力
because you know for all we fuck you know you guys might make it me included.
包括我在内 大家都知道
It might make it like 1.79 Rubber Ducky or something like that.
就像类似是1.79橡胶鸭子或者类似的名字
Oh god, that'd be so funny.
哦天哪这肯定很有趣
But anyways, um, I can't be the only one who read this as Type 90,
不说这个了 我肯定不是唯一一个这样读90式的
the light weight heavy Hitler.
轻量级的重型希特拉
Okay.
好吧
This is the world we're living now
现在我们这个社会
that in 2018 even when there's nothing to be offended by
尽管2018年没有那么招人烦的存在
or to be triggered by
或者刺激人的存在
your brain makes you triggered.
你有时还是会自己吓自己
It's the damn chemtrails.
这只不过是某种既视感而已
But today as you might have guessed we're going to be talking about the Type 90
正如你所料 今天我们要讲90式
and how it's long overdue and much needed for Japan.
对于日本陆战科技树而言 这是早该完成且亟待解决的问题
However though, we're gonna be talking about how War Thunder needs to serve us better
不过呢 我们现在要讲的是战雷该如何更好地吸引玩家
and I'll try an analogy.
我将做一个类比
And we'll do this first.
我们先分析这个
I think we all can agree that the biggest moneymaker for War Thunder is new content
我们都认为战雷主要是靠推出新内容来赚钱
in the terms of new vehicles to grind for to get frustrated for
譬如说推出新载具让大家肝的那种研发
or to use golden eagles to buy new premiums and to buy bundles.
或者是用金鹰买金币载具或者是礼包
New content is the biggest supplier of money for free-to-play we all know that.
我们知道新内容是免费游戏最大的资金来源
War Thunder has to pay bills.
战雷需要赚钱
It's a multi-million dollar company.
这是个价值数百万美元的公司
There's so much logistics involved that they have to make money to keep this game alive.
这之中需要太多机制来让Gaijin赚钱并让这个游戏持续运营下去
We know that.
我们知道
And that's why in every update major update.
这就是为什么每次大版本更新的时候
Boom! New shiny toys to play with,
哇 又有很多新玩具玩了
to hide the other factors that might make this game redundant.
从而遮掩了那些游戏中有问题的部分
What I would love to see the War Thunder team do
我所希望战雷的开发团队做的事情
is to serve us dinner every big patch.
是每个大版本都能让人眼前一亮
Bear with me.
等我一会
So for appetizers, think as appetizers of like a recap of what happened from the last update to this update,
对于开胃菜 或者说是一个梗概 从上次更新到这次更新
so this would explain the things that they fixed or were updated since the last big patch
这些标明了自从上次大版本更新之后他们修复或者更新的东西
such as bugs, an economy changes, BR changes
譬如软件问题 经济问题 权重改变
pretty much this a way to be transparent
这些浅显的东西
and to lay out what they have tried to do,
再看看他们做的东西
depends on how you want to look at it, to improve the game for the better
这取决于你希望游戏变好的立场
because right now every patch is just like
因为现在的这些版本就像
Boom! Abrams. T-64. Type 90.
快看 Abrams T-64 90式
and a lot of the things that they do behind the scenes that do improve the game for better
当然也有许多Gaijin在游戏背后的努力来让游戏变得更好
or for worse are overshadowed by new shiny pixels.
或者变得更差 而这些都隐匿在光鲜的外表之下
Now for the main course or the entrée.
而真正的大问题 也就是主菜是
Show the big flashy tanks and planes and carry on business as usual.
就如以往一般把这些光鲜亮丽的载具持续推出
We need new content into the game
我们需要游戏加入新的内容
but we also need everything in a nice balanced
但我们也需要游戏中的各种事物得到很好的平衡
a nice Yin and Yang.
就像阴阳那样
So this is where dessert would come in.
现在到了甜（总）点（结）时间
This might be a stretch
我说得有些太多了
but War Thunder could use this course as a chance to explain its plans for the longevity of this game
但是战雷可以利用这个契机来解释他们对持续运营游戏的计划
such as updates for new game modes and development
譬如更新游戏模式
and during confrontation, World War mode
开发一些新的对抗模式譬如世界大战模式
or even new game modes that I believe could fit in this game.
或者那些更适合游戏的模式
However it's been battled, conquest, domination
不过 现在说的这些都被取消了
and maybe a little bit of break for four years.
而且很可能接下来的四年内都不会有大的改变
I think that's a bismal.
我认为这是偷懒
I think that's a lack of effort.
缺乏努力
And even further I think they're taking the easy way out with this method.
说得重一点 他们不过是用这个方法搪塞而已
They're going for the easy buck.
应付
The guaranteed buck.
本应是他们该好好完成的责任
The guaranteed way to make money through this game
而是更稳健地通过游戏赚钱
and that it's core. It's a really good way to make money
这是关键 这确实是个赚钱的好方法
until there's no more new content to add.
在用尽新内容之前
There's no more new vehicles.
而那时就没有这么多新载具了
There is a fine night amount of vehicles we can add in War Thunder.
能加入战雷的载具是有限的
吐槽:
深邃黑暗幻想
It's not a fantasy game.
这不是一个空想出来的游戏
Only things that have been protoType built will be in the game.
只有那些造出过原型的载具能被加入游戏
They're gonna run out at some point in time
以后的某个时间点上 会用光的
and at that point of time they're gonna have to rely on the game mechanics,
而在那时 他们就必须依赖于游戏机制的吸引力
the game modes and events to keep the game fresh
或者是游戏模式和活动来让游戏保持新鲜
and to keep players coming back.
从而保持玩家的活跃度
And back to the analogy this is what the dessert category allows.
回到这个类推 这就像是甜点种类
It allows War Thunder a platform to show what they're building for the longevity for the game.
我们将会看到战雷这个平台是如何应对游戏持续运营这个问题的
What new environment,
新的环境
what new game modes we can use on our new shiny tanks,
新的坦克将用于何种新的游戏模式
on our new shiny planes on.
或者是新的飞机
Because right now,
因为现在
it's redundant and doesn't matter how many times you reskin a tank,
无论你如何更换涂装 你的新载具（在目前的游戏机制下）都显得多余
it's the same thing over and over again.
总是这样
Ok, so the Type 90 the lightweight heavy Hitler, huh,
好吧 再讲回轻量级的重型希特拉
hitter, I don't know why they would tag it like that,
击球手 我不知道他们为什么要这么叫
because maybe it is a lightweight heavy hitter.
也许它就是个轻量级的实力击球手
I don't know I see this thing weigh 50 tons.
我不太清楚他们这么说的目的 明明有50吨
So let's go ahead and read the dev blog a little bit
那我们再接着看看开发博客
um this Wow so the Type 90 was to replace the outdated Type 61
90式是用来取代过时的61式
oh and Type 74. See look look guys.
哦 还有74式 瞧瞧
They they said that the Type 74 is outdated.
他们居然说74式是过时的了
Even though it's at 8.7.
尽管它是8.7权重的
This is absolutely ridiculous.
这绝对足够荒谬
There's such a big span of warfare in War Thunder.
在战雷里如此巨大跨度的战争当中
The whole row right is a vehicle you can use in War Thunder
在战雷里的科技树
and you can go all the way up now to a Type 90.
你现在甚至可以研发到90式
Absolutely ridiculous.
太荒谬了
This thing was produced from 1990
这个坦克是1990年生产的
when I wasn't even born yet.
那年我还没出生
One more year to go.
还差一年
But it stopped production in 2009 when I was a junior in high school.
但是在2009年 也就是我高三的时候停产了
This is pretty nice of War Thunder.
这确实是战雷的一个优势
They say the Type 90 will be available to all players as a new top tier vehicles.
他们说所有玩家都可以玩到作为新顶级载具的90式
So they'll just give it out for free, no grinding required.
也就意味着这不需要花钱 同时也不需要研发
For this rank six vehicles.
对于这辆6级载具而言
I am joking. That means it's not premium.
我只是开玩笑 这意味着这不是金币载具
You're going to have to lose left nut and left leg to be able to drive this thing.
为了研发出这个东西 <del>你可能会肝功能衰竭</del>
Now this is much needed for Japan.
不过对于日本科技树而言 这是急需的
Much needed.
必需的
Japan was a
日系呢
since probably even the MBT, T-64 era MBTs or the modern stuff being added to the game,
差不多是在MBT-70 T-64等现代坦克加入游戏时
they really they weren't sought-after as much as the other nations.
日系玩家他们确实不像其他国家那样吃香
Because they didn't have the top dog new toy.
因为他们并没有新的顶级载具
And nothing has been done about it.
而且并没有任何新的措施来解决这个问题
They might have gotten a twin-engine fighter here and there.
他们可能在科技树的各种位置得到了各种各样的双发飞机
But no big substantial changes to the Ground Force tech tree.
但是对于陆战科技树的改变还不够多不够大
Now it's here though.
而现在我们有了
And this will be competitive at top BR, top dog MBT tank here we go.
而这将使得日系在顶级房有足够多的竞争力
Now on to the specs of the Type 90.
再看看90式的参数
The gun we're gonna talk about is absolute 100% being added with the tank.
我们讨论的坦克炮肯定是坦克上的那门
The armor take it with a grain of salt.
但是装甲可能就是假的
Because we don't know.
因为我们不知道
I'm gonna go off a Wikipedia that hasn't had correct citation.
我去维基百科看过了 数据没有正确的引用
So we'll just push that on through and open a discussion in the comments below
所以我们仍将讨论下去 欢迎大家在评论区发表意见
of the believed armor values of the Type 90.
关于90式的可信装甲数据
So the Type 90 has a hundred and twenty millimeter gun
而90式有一门120mm炮
that is pretty similar to the Leopard 2K.
类似于豹2K
The big difference here is that this hundred and twenty millimeter cannon is auto reloading.
而这之中最大的区别是这是一门自动装填的120mm炮
So the Leopard 2K I think base manual reload speed is eight point seven seconds.
而豹2K的基本手动装填时间是8.7秒
There's been talks of this hundred and twenty millimeter auto reloading gun
关于这个自动装填的120mm炮 已经有一些讨论
that could reload in three to five seconds.
可以在3到5秒内完成重装填
Now this is War Thunder and not all reloads are historical.
当然这是战雷 不是所有装填时间是符合史实的
A lot of them aren't historical.
许多数据都不符合史实
So I'm going to assume right now this 120 millimeter will reload somewhere at five seconds to maybe even six
所以我会假定这个自动装填时间大概会在5到6秒
if we're lucky, maybe five point five around there.
运气好的话也许在5.5秒左右
I think that's a balanced reload for 120mm.
对于120mm炮 这将是一个较为平衡的时间
So I've been trying to find a concise answer for the armor.
我正在寻找这个装甲数据的简单回答
At least number-wise for the Type 90 and it's all over the place.
至少是90式的数据 而这到处都是
So this can go anywhere War Thunderer's probably digging up some secret documents about it.
所以这将取决于战雷挖掘出的什么秘密文件
But I'll try to relay some of the stuff I found.
当然我会传递我所找到的数据
A lot of places say the armor is classified.
许多人都说这个装甲数据是保密的
Some places throw out numbers
而有些地方则泄漏出了数据
such as the turret can protect against 550 millimeters of kinetic energy or kinetic round
譬如炮塔可以防护动能弹的550mm穿深
as well as defeat 850 millimeter penned chemical rounds.
同时防护850mm穿深的化学能弹
注:
搭载JM-33 120mm弹种的说法来自维基百科Type 90 Kyū-maru词条下的Design-Armor目录
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Type_90_Ky%C5%AB-maru
Other places say it is proved against the Japanese for the JM-33 120mm round
而其他地方则说 这能抵挡日本使用的JM-33 120mm炮弹
that does have a penetration of 480 millimeters to 550 millimeters kinetic apfsds.
这种尾翼稳定脱壳穿甲弹 也就是动能弹的穿深大概在480mm到550mm之间
So if anything from the development time period and the advancement of ceramics etc.
根据这段开发时期发生的事情 以及陶瓷技术的进步等等
This I believe will be a stronger heads-up tank than the Abrams.
这将比Abrams还要强
This is only for the front turret only.
这当然说的只是炮塔前部的防御
I have no information on the lower glacis, the upper glacis, the side hull etc.
我没有任何关于首上 手下 侧面装甲的数据
Just when the turret is looking directly at you in the turret only.
只是炮塔正面
Those are the numbers-ish.
这些也就是些数字
Now for the side turret if you get a side shot on this turret,
对于炮塔侧面
you will always be able to go through if you're using a main gun.
如果你使用主炮的炮弹 那你可能能击穿
Anti-air, 30 mils, they shouldn't be able to go through.
防空炮 30mm的这些东西 应该没可能击穿它
The Type 90 side turret was designed to counter 35 millimeter APDS rounds.
90式的炮塔侧面能抵御35mm的脱壳穿甲弹
Now I said before the main guns absolutely they will slice right through
当然 炮塔侧面肯定无法抵御主炮射击
but will they slice through too much or too quickly without being able to spawn or shrapnel.
但是难以产生一击必杀那么多的弹片
Time will tell.
以后就知道了
However, the downside of having an auto loader is that usually you have one less crew member
当然了 自动装弹机的坏处在于更少的坦克乘员数量
which means the Type 90 only has 3 crew members.
而在90式上面 就意味着它只有3个乘员
So survivability if you get cruise shots into the Type 90
如果击穿了90式
is gonna be pretty darn low.
那么它的生存几率很可能非常低
Also things dimension is that, this tank does have blowout panels.
同样是生存几率这个角度 这个坦克也有防爆门
So expect it to function like an M1 Abrams already in game.
所以可以期待它能发挥出类似Abrams在游戏中的表现
Last but not least though, the Type 90 is equipped with a 1510 cylinder diesel horsepower.
最后 90式搭载了一个1510马力的柴油机
Excuse me guys.
抱歉
Horsepower engine that brings this beast up to 70 kilometers an hour in forward
这个引擎能驱动坦克前进最快70km/h
and 32 in Reverse.
而倒车最快32km/h
So we're gonna really like this tank.
所以我们可能会沉迷于这辆坦克
This is gonna be a very enjoyable tank to play.
玩这个坦克将会非常享受
We're just going to see the armor values on the whole in turret
我们将会看到炮塔装甲的完整数据
to see what is the best course of action for taking this thing out on the battlefield.
看看这个坦克最适合的玩法是什么
Guys hope you have enjoyed this video today.
希望今天大家喜欢这个视频
Thanks for hanging out.
谢谢大家抽出时间
Thanks for watching.
谢谢观看
Letting you guys know that I am streaming today.
我今天（2018.05.11）会直播
Check Twitter.
看看推特
Check the future live streams.
看看以后的直播计划
It might be soon. It might be now.
也许就最近一段时间
But I'll be live today.
但是我今天肯定会直播
Then guys hope you have enjoyed.
希望大家看得愉快
Have a great day.
祝你度过愉悦的一天